I would like to show how easy it is to
install Cu I am T encoder first take the
spacer wrench and place it over the
shaft select the proper sleeve to fit
the shaft size and press it down tight
against the wrench take the shaft
adapter and press it on over the sleeve
use the centering tool to press it down
tight
once that is snapped into place you can
remove the spacer wrench next will be to
take the mounting bracket and center it
over the shaft adapter using the
centering tool at which point we can
screw it in place now that the mounting
plate is secured and centered simply
snap in your Cu I am T encoder and it's
ready to use
cui AMT encoder series includes mt 1 0
mt 1 1 a.m. t20 mt 3 1 all of which can
be found at digikey.com thanks for
watching