(energetic light rock music)
- I would like to show how easy it is
to install a CUI AMT encoder.
First, take the spacer wrench
and place it over the shaft.
Select the proper sleeve
to fit the shaft size,
and press it down tight,
against the wrench.
Take the shaft adapter, and
press it on over the sleeve.
Use the centering tool,
to press it down tight.
Once that is snapped into place,
you can remove the spacer wrench.
Next, we'll need to take
the mounting bracket
and center it over the shaft adapter
using the centering tool.
At which point, we can screw it in place.
Now that the mounting plate
is secured and centered,
simply snap in your CUI AMT encoder
and it's ready to use.
CUI's AMT encoder series includes AMT10,
AMT11,
AMT20,
AMT31.
All of which can be found at digikey.com.
Thanks for watching.
^(energetic light rock music)