[Music]
welcome to the AMT encoder series
installation tutorial where we'll
outline the steps required to accurately
mount an AMT encoder onto a motor
[Music]
begin by inserting tool a as a spacer
that defines the distance to the
mounting surface slide the appropriate
size sleeve onto the shaft and all the
way down to two La slide the shaft
adapter over the sleeve
use Tulsi to press the shaft adapter
over the sleeve until it is flush with
to LA
[Music]
remove tools a and C
use Tulsi as a centering tool for
mounting the AMT base onto the motor
[Music]
carefully engage the groove in Tulsi to
align with the flange on the base
[Music]
slide the bass and Tulsi onto the motor
centering on to the shaft adapter fasten
the base onto the motor
remove Tulsi
[Music]
snap the amt top cover onto the base
carefully observing that the teeth of
the shaft adapter aligned with the
grooves in the hub
[Music]
make sure the snaps are fully engaged
and the top covers flush with a base
align the lip on the reverse side of
Tulsi with the opening on the top cover
and push Tulsi until it is flush with
the front of the top government when
installation is finished the shaft
adapter sleeve and rotor hub should all
be recessed slightly from the front of
the encoder with the motor shaft
rotating freely thank you for watching
our AMT Series installation tutorial for
more information or support please email
us at AMT support at cui comm or visit
our website at wwe.com thanks for
watching